Today, I will show off a demo
of the Nemo claw blueprint and how we
use this inside of Nvidia.
We find that with many open source
projects in Nvidia, we need to balance
the asks of the open source community
with internal priorities driving our
product forward.
And to do that,
we need to triage those needs into a
singular roadmap.
The example we will take a look at today
is one that we have deployed internally
at Nvidia.
And you can do the same.
It is shown in our Nemo claw community
repository.
I'll switch over to a quick view of the
architecture diagram here.
We want to create an agent deployed
internally that can accomplish this. And
in this case, we used a Hermes agent
developed by News Research.
For the agent to accomplish these tasks,
it needs access to internal data.
But we don't want an agent with that
type of access to also be able to write
to external sources.
Additionally, API tokens used to access
services like GitHub, Slack, and Outlook
shouldn't be accessible to these agents.
So, how can we maintain a balance
between deploying a powerful agent to
accomplish these tasks while
establishing trust boundaries?
We use Nvidia Open Shell and define
policies that will allow us to access
that internal data
while preventing the agent from posting
it externally.
Within that repository,
there is a full setup guide that will
take you through cloning the repo
to installing Open Shell,
authenticating with tools like Outlook,
and bringing up that agent in Open
Shell.
Now that we've done the setup
and we've deployed the agent, we can
interact the agent by messaging it
directly in Slack.
You can ask it questions like, "Can you
tell me a little bit about yourself or
what kind of agent you are?" And it
says, "Well, I'm an AI assistant running
inside of Nvidia's Open Shell Sandbox.
It has access to skills, persistent
memory."
You can ask it, "Well, tell me about the
skills." And it will tell you all of the
skills that it has.
These can be skills defined by Hermes,
built-in, or these can be custom skills.
"What kinds of custom skills did we
provide to this particular agent?" Well,
you can ask it that. And it will tell
you, "Here are all the skills." And you
can go and verify in the Nemo Clock
community repo that these are actually
the skills that we have provided the
agent.
Additionally,
we can show the power of Hermes in its
ability to self-evolve. For example,
you might want to ask for an update of
all of the issues for a product seen
across various channels like GitHub,
developer forums, and internal clients.
To do this,
I might start by asking for a daily
update on the important issues for Nemo
Clock. And it provides me one. It gives
me
a title,
some issues, say five of them, and some
discussions along with a bottom line.
Perhaps I like this format initially,
but
I want to change it a little bit. And
so, I ask, "Can you give me a TLDR at
the very top, a too long, didn't read?"
So that if I didn't want to dig into all
the issues, I can just read through that
and get the gist of what's happening.
And of course, the agent says, "Sure,
happy to do that. I can give you a
little bit of uh
background before I give you more
details. So that if you don't have time,
you can go through and just read the
very basics of it."
If I don't want the bottom line,
I can ask it, "Please don't give me the
bottom line."
But now that I'm happy with this
particular format,
if you say, "Hey, I'd like a
reliable way of receiving this type of
format if I ask you a similar question."
It will go ahead
and create a skill for you. You don't
have to say, "Create a skill for me." It
just knows to do that.
Finally, once the agent learns this
skill, it can be used across the
communication channels, including
Outlook.
And we can see that here.
Here I have emailed my agent and I've
asked it for the latest daily digest for
Nemo claw in the usual format.
And it responds to me.
It says, "Here's the digest
with the format that I've learned over
time
with the title,
the TLDR,
the top five issues alongside some links
that are important,
and the discussions, and no bottom
line."
This shows the usefulness of
self-evolution
within a Hermes agent, deployed securely
via NVIDIA Open Shell, and powered by
our Nematron models.
Feel free to take a look at it at the
Nemo claw community repository for this
example and more.